ipal.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This website is committed to ensuring your personal information is protected. This privacy policy was created to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle any information we receive from you. This privacy policy only applies to transactions and activities in which you engage, and data gathered, on This website(and double blind email communications between This website members) (collectively, the "Site") but does not apply to any other Website or offline point of contact between this website, or any other company, and consumers, that we do not control.

Please note this website reserves the right to change our privacy policy at any time. If such a change occurs you will be notified via our Site. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time.

If you have any issues with the content on our site or with this privacy statement or the way your personal information is being handled please contact this website.

**Your IP Address**

Each time you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address, the website Cookie information and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize the Site for you and to diagnose problems with our Site, we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

**Cookies**

Cookie files written to your computer are used for record keeping purposes on some sites, including this website. We can also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password, and if you choose, to save other personal and financial information so you do not have to reenter it each time you visit the Site. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. To disable these cookies, simply go to the "help" portion of the toolbar on your browser and this should tell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas on the Site.

**What We Collect From You**

We collect personal information from you. We do this in order to operate the Site and to occasionally display advertisements about products or services that may be of interest to you. Personal Information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. We also collect "financial information" such as your credit card numbers or passwords. Further, we collect certain "demographic information", that is information that is neither personal information nor financial information; this may include, but is not limited to, zip code, gender, username, and age/birth date.

We do NOT knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18, as we require that all users represent to us that they are at least 18 years old.

**What Other Website Collect From You**

Our Site contains links to other websites. You need to be aware that when you click on these links and visit these other websites, (regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property), we do NOT control these other websites or these other websites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other websites. Each of these websites should have its own Privacy Policy if it is collecting personal information about you. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

**How We Use Personal Information**

We use your email address and your other personal information to help us efficiently operate the Site, to contact you in connection with your membership and other activities on the Site (including, but not limited to, confirmation emails or important news that could affect your relationship with this website), and to forward messages to you from other website users. These types of communications are known as "Operational Communications."

To operate the Site, we may share your personal information with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, email origination, receipt or support services, and customer relationship management services. We require these entities not to use your information for any other purpose.

Any third party with whom we are allowed to share your personal information is authorized to use your personal information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Those who contact you will need to be instructed directly by you regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them.

Please read the information below under the heading "Special Cases in which we Share Personal and Financial Information" to learn more ways in which we may share your personal information.

**How We Use Financial Information**

We use your financial information to, if applicable, check your qualifications and to bill you our service. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information, on the Site, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine are necessary to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your credit card issuer for their purposes. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support the transaction or activity.

**Special Cases in which we Share Personal and Financial Information**

Your personal information or financial information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets, or a bankruptcy or to comply with the law or to protect the interests or safety of this website or other visitors to the Site.

**How We Use Public Information and Other Demographic Information**

We may review all your demographic information. We may use public information to enable other users to determine whether they are a match for you and to communicate with you. We may use demographic information to tailor the Site and communications to your interests. We may also share demographic information with advertisers on an anonymous and aggregated basis (i.e., without telling the advertisers your identity). One of the reasons we may do this is to increase the likelihood that our advertisers' goods and services will appeal to the website's users, so that we may target specific ads at specific demographic groups. Our sharing of demographic information with advertisers is anonymous (i.e., we do not tell advertisers which particular the website users are members of which demographic groups), subject to the rest of this privacy policy. When you respond to an advertisement, however, we ask you to remember that if that ad that is targeted to a demographic group and you decide to give the advertiser your personal information, then the advertiser may be able to identify you as being a member of that demographic group.

**Our Security Precautions**

The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. We encrypt all of your personal and financial information as it travels over the Internet and we store your financial information on our servers in encrypted form. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computer networks which may be located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in which you reside, and the country or jurisdiction in which these computer networks are located may not have privacy laws as protective as the laws in your country or jurisdiction.

**Changing our Privacy Policy for Previously Gathered Information**

If at any point we decide to use particular personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email or by providing 30 days notice on the Site. Please note that we will continue to have the right to change our privacy policy and practices, and how we use your personally identifiable information, without notice, as described in the first paragraph of this Privacy Policy, provided that such changes shall only apply to information gathered on or after the date of the change.

**How You Can Access and Update Your Email Preferences, Personal Information and Public Information**

We give you the opportunity to modify personal information or demographic information you have provided to us, at anytime. Please be aware that it may take several hours for the changes you make to take effect on the public areas of the Site. We thank you for your patience. Please note that changing or deleting your information, will only change or delete the data in our database for purposes of future activities on the Site and for managing future communications from this website. These changes and deletions will not change or delete emails or information that we may have already forwarded to other users or credit card companies or any other third parties, all as provided above in this privacy policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, please contact us.
